Come on Meena, sit quickly.  [MUSIC]
[SCREAMING]
Oh, help me, somebody help me.
Hey brother, what happened brother?  What happened?  I was
taking my younger brother to the doctor
and this accident happened.
[MUSIC]
Brother, her body is so hot.
Brother, he had fever, that's why I was going to the doctor.
Brother, I am a small doctor.  I will bring down the fever here.
Yes brother, bring down the fever.  It will be very kind of you.
[MUSIC]
Look, his body has cooled down.
Hey you quack doctor, you will kill my brother.
Doctor sir, please save my brother,
doctor sir.  You stay here.
Wait, be patient.   The
patient needs blood.  You
bring blood quickly.  Yes doctor sir, I will bring the blood right away.  The
doctor brought the blood.   He
brought the blood very quickly.  Doctor sir, this is
fake blood.
Hey crazy people, how will you burn fake blood?
Hey doctor sir, you know it is fake blood.
We know it's fake blood.  But my
brother doesn't know that it is fake blood.
[Laughter]